Finding Aid for francisco
Clarke Historical Library
- Francisco Photography Studio Photographic Collection is open for research.
  - Miscellaneous Smaller Photographs, Left side, Back, of the box, Wilmat, [no first name],September 16, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 531)
  - Miscellaneous Smaller Photographs, Left side, Back, of the box, Wongeshik, [no first name],September 7, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 532)
  - Miscellaneous Smaller Photographs, Left side, Back, of the box, Yoder, Rachell,May 5, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 533)
  - Miscellaneous Smaller Photographs, Left side, Back, of the box, Unidentified Photographs (10 envelopes),undated (Box 6, Folder 534)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Ace Hardware Store (3 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Aldon Rug Mills (2 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Ballman, Bob - Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Basketball - Boys Team, Sacred Heart Academy,undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Bellinger, Cecil - Copy,April 4, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Bissette, Ed -Wedding,November 28, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Black, Ed, Mrs. - Copy, Koda Br. E.,August 27, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Bourland, Jim - Family (2 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Brixby, Ed - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Casfard, Harry - Copy,undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Cashen, L.D. Myers Storefront,undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Cemetery - McClintric Gravestone,undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Circle X Cowboys (Country Band) - Earl, Jeff, Geo., Chum,1950 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Cline Advertising Agency - Copy,September 8, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Comers Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Commencement Photograph - Beal City High School (BCHS),1923 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Commencement Photograph, Unidentified,undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Confiscated Stills,undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Conners, Frank - Copy,undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Consumers Power Company, Mount Pleasant, Michigan,undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Crapo Agency,undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Crawford, Arnold - Softball Team,1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Cummings, Chas.,undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Curtiss, Arlo - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Deer Antlers,undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Deer Hunting - Man with a Dead Deer,undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Elliott, Elsie (Klumpp) - Copy, Daylite, 1 sec.,undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Esch, Lewis - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Fadink Family - Weidman Carnival Accident group around coffin outside of house, wedding, 2 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Faltz, John - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Family, Carl - H Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Family Photograph - Unidentified,1948-1951 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Fedeiva, Robt. - Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Feltman, Wilbert - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Fish,undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Flynn, Bud (2 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Flynn, ORM - Copy,undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Fox, W.J. - Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Frick, August, Sr. - Family,August 13, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Frick, Frank - 5 Girls,1963 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Frick, Otto - 4 Children,April 10, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Gamary, Matt,undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Gates, Earl - Family, 5,undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Gepford, Bill - Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Gover, N.D. - Retouched,undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Gover, Liquidatings Store, 2 envelopes,undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Graham, Donald Frederick - Air Force Dismissal Report,November 7, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Graham, Henry,undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Group Photograph, Unidentified,undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Gruss, Joe - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Gruss, Joe - Family,Christmas 1961 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Gruss, Richard - Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Herrington Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Howard, Tom - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Hutchinson, Orval - Wedding (2 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Jewell, W. - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Klumpp, Kendall,undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Leffingwell, Floyd,May 5, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Leonard, Alfred - Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Maniteau, W.R. - Wedding,October 19, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, McBride, Ruth Putney,August 3, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, McDonald, Fred - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, McNeel, W. Bundy - Saw Mill,undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Men in Uniform - Unidentified,undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Michigan Bowhunters' Annual Banquet,1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Millington, Don - Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Montgomery, Ward - Velox F3 SW,undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Mount Pleasant Hardware,1956 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Murphy, Mike, Smithers Building,April 19, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Myers, Robt. - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Nagy, Mike - Gas Station,August 4, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, National Field Archery Association Club Banquet,February 24, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Owen, Chas. - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Quillen, Joe - Velox F3 SW,undated (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Renwick, Howard, Mrs.,May 6, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Rice, Lester,undated (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Rinard, Robt. - Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Russell, Walter - Village President,November 10, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Russell, Walter,1957 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Ryzenga, John - Wedding,September 11, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Scene, Country Road - Bridge Out,undated (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Scene, Street,undated (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Schoen, Omar, Houghtaling Casket Photograph (2 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Schumacher, Ed, Mrs. (3 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Schumacher, Keith - 7 Girls,undated (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Seeley, Earl - Family Group,undated (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Sellers, Blanc - Copy,undated (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Simmer, Paul (3 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Softball, Girls - Picken's Girls 1949 Champs,1949 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Softball, Girls - Picken's,[1949] (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Straus, Art (4 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Theilen, Bob - Wedding,February 1956 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Theilen, Pete - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Theisen, Frank - Family (2 envelopes),October 27, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Thering, Elmer - Family (3 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Thering, Tom - Wedding (5 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Times News - Copy,undated (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Torpey, Hilton - Wedding (5 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Watson, Lloyd - Family,undated (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Weber, Ben - Wedding,undated (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Wedding Photographs - Unidentified (4 envelopes),1948-1951 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Wedding Photographs - Unidentified (4 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - 8 x 10 inch Negatives, Unidentified Photographs (7 envelopes),undated (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot,February 1961 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 1 of 2),February 1961-January 1962 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 2 of 2),February 1961-January 1962 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 1 of 2),December 1962-August 1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 2 of 2),December 1962-August 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 1 of 2),August 1963-October 1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 2 of 2),August 1963-October 1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot,December 1964-August 1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 1 of 2),August 1965-November 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 2 of 2),August 1965-November 1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 1 of 2),November 1969-January 1970 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 8 x 10 inch Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 2 of 2),November 1969-January 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 1 of 2),November 1958-July 1959 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (folder 2 of 2),November 1958-July 1959 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot,July 1959-January 1960 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot,January 1960-July 1960 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot,December 1960-February 1961 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 1 of 2),February 1961-October 1961 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 2 of 2),February 1961-October 1961 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 1 of 2),February 1962-October 1962 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 2 of 2),February 1962-October 1962 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 1 of 2),November 1964-December 1964 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 2 of 2),November 1964-December 1964 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 1 of 2),December 1964-July 1965 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 2 of 2),December 1964-July 1965 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot,July 1965-December 1965 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot,December 1965-April 1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 1 of 2),January 1968-November 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 2 of 2),January 1968-November 1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 1 of 2),November 1967-October 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - mostly 5.5 x 6 inches or smaller Black and White Unidentified Photographs, by date taken or reshot (Folder 2 of 2),November 1967-October 1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Abbey, Omea,November 7, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Astavab, Rorella,April 31, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Baker, Dorothy,December 22, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Bech, [no first name],October 13, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Beck, Grace,September 13, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Bilcox, Mary,June 11, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Bissette, Carol,June 20, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Cabin, H.A.,July 1939 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Chippeway, Walter,June 13, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Cojpens, Carol,May 1955 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Collins, Ruth Ann,September 12, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Coon, Nancy,December 20, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Coppens, [no first name],December 3, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Darfueres, [no first name],October 19, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Diggers, Albert,January 5, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Donald, Jolin,July 12, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Eggleston, [no first name],May 15, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Erway, Ida,November 16, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Gase, [no first name],August 11, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Gibson, June,August 8, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Gill, Betty,April 5, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Goldhecker, [no first name],June 16, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Gross, Francis,October 9, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Haggart, Rosehauty M. - #1,undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Hanesworth, Don,March 13, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Hoover, Jack,March 27, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Johnson, Frank,June 7, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Kahlgegab, Yvonne,August 6, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Kennedy, Virgil,May 12, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Langejans, [no first name],August 13-16, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Machuta, Fruuh,February 27, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Mangris, Ethel,September 25, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Martin, K.P.,April 27, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Martin, Mary,April 22, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, McGuirk, Joan,May 12, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Mount Pleasant, Michigan [copies],undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Mullin, Bernice,March 2, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Neyome, Margaret,July 2, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, O'Holliday, W.,July 12, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Pitts, Helen,September 3, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Rhodes, Bill,July 7, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Roberts, Jim,September 25, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Rydman, M.,February 25, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Savage, Ges,June 22, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Schafer, Tex,January 27, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Shigibard, W.,September 8, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Steele, [no first name] (2),November 3, 1948; December 4, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Streber, [no first name],March 3, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Strong, L.,October 8, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Swarty, [no first name],January 14, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Throw, Henry,April 5, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Trussell, Bud,undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Tyman, Dale,October 31, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Watson, Sally,February 19, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Williams, John,March 2, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Wright, Lily,February 10, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Yonker, Clifford,February 23, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Yunker, [no first name],June 25, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Zygmunt, L.,October 23, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Unidentified (folder 1 of 7),undated (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Unidentified (folder 2 of 7),undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Unidentified (folder 3 of 7),undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Unidentified (folder 4 of 7),undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Unidentified (folder 5 of 7),undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Unidentified (folder 6 of 7),undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Various 3.5 x 4 inches and Small Sized Photographs and Negatives, Unidentified (folder 7 of 7),undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Francisco Family Photographs (Various Sizes), Some Identified,1927-1964 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Francisco Family Photographs (Various Sizes), Unidentified (folder 1 of 6),undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Francisco Family Photographs (Various Sizes), Unidentified (folder 2 of 6),undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Francisco Family Photographs (Various Sizes), Unidentified (folder 3 of 6),undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Francisco Family Photographs (Various Sizes), Unidentified (folder 4 of 6),undated (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Francisco Family Photographs (Various Sizes), Unidentified (folder 5 of 6),undated (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Francisco Family Photographs (Various Sizes), Unidentified (folder 6 of 6),undated (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Francisco Family Negatives,undated (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Oversized Folder, Francisco Family Photographs (folder 1 of 4),undated (Folder 1)
  - Oversized Folder, Francisco Family Photographs (folder 2 of 4),undated (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folder, Francisco Family Photographs (folder 3 of 4),undated (Folder 3)
  - Oversized Folder, Francisco Family Photographs (folder 4 of 4),undated (Folder 4)